Mingle All the Way is a romance, comedy, tv movie film directed by Allan Harmon.
Molly is determined to prove to her family that her new networking app—designed to pair busy
professionals together for upcoming events, without long-term romance—is a success.
When Molly joins Mingle All the Way and is matched with Jeff, they are both horrified to
realize they’ve already had not one, but two disastrous previous encounters.
Molly Hoffman, played by Jen Lilley.
Jeff Scanlon, played by Brant Daugherty.
Veronica Hoffman, played by Lindsay Wagner.
Harris, played by Casey Manderson.
Lisa Turner, played by Sandy Sidhu.
Erica Fielding, played by April Telek.
Kutu Ma Kutu, also known as Kutu Ma Kutu Supari Dana (Nepali:कुटुमा कुटु or कुटुमा कुटु
सुपारी दाना) is a Nepalese song from the 2017 Nepalese film Dui Rupaiya.
The song is sung by Rajan Raj Shiwakoti, Melina Rai and Rajan Ishan, with
lyrics and music by Prashidhika Tiwari, directed by Asim Shah.
The music video of the track features actors Asif Shah,
Nischal Basnet, Swastima Khadka and Buddhi Tamang.
On 22 December 2017 Kutu Ma Kutu became the first Nepalese YouTube video to reach 100 million views and it is the most viewed Nepalese video on YouTube currently
viewing over 200 million times, also it was the fastest song to gain 20 million views and in 49 days the song managed to gain 10 Million views.
The name "Kutu Ma Kutu" is a Neologism that refers as the word kutu kutu mean something
that is hard when chewing it and the word supari dana means Areca nut.
The word is usually used to invite someone to a function than
you chew the nut to accept the invitation.
You can read kutu ma kutu lyrics .
The film explores themes of friendship, holiday,
business woman, christmas, dating app.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.